

Website: <u>@jfelipepv</u> felipe23pena@gmail.com +57 3183946191

A multimedia engineer passionate with a solid approach in user experience (UX), user interface design (UI) and graphic design. My professional path has been centered on making shocking digital experiences and attractive ones that merge the creativity with the functionality. With a solid formation and practical experience in these areas, I have contributed to the success of various projects and work teams.

Experience

Partner Comunicación / Web Designer

NOV 2023 - PRESENT

I transform ideas into impactful digital experiences, working closely with clients to create visually appealing and functional websites, optimized for mobile devices and aligned with their business goals.

Orión Estudio / Junior Web Designer

FEB 2023 - OCT 2023

Supported the design and development of websites, as well as the creation of content calendars. Conducted research on trends and innovations in marketing, advertising, and web development to generate strategic ideas and contribute to internal initiatives.

Acsendo / Designer

JUL 2022 - DEC 2022

Assisted in the design and production of graphic materials for Acsendo's communications, actively contributing to the company's branding and positioning with current clients, potential leads, and internal stakeholders.

Education

Universidad Autónoma de Occidente

Multimedia Engineering 2017 – 2023

Academic Achievements

<u>Platzi</u> / UX/UI Designer 2023 - Present

Skills and Languages

Skills:

Wireframes · Mock ups · Prototype · User testing · Data analysis · Communicative · Detail-oriented · Figma · Strategic thinking · Design system · Style guide · User experience (UX) · User interface design (UI) · HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript · Adobe Creative Suite · Graphic design

Languages:

Spanish (Native) English (Intermediate)